The target has appeared.
타겟이 나타났습니다.
Can shoot.
촬영할 수 있습니다.
Wait.
기다리다.
It's not like the woman came to cooperate,
여자가 협조하러 온 것도 아니고,
clearly knew there was danger, why didn't he leave?
위험이 있다는 것을 분명히 알고 있었는데 왜 떠나지 않았습니까?
If I retreat, you won't be able to retreat.
내가 후퇴하면 너희도 후퇴할 수 없을 것이다.
Several snipers,
여러 명의 저격수,
currently can only confirm one.
현재는 하나만 확인할 수 있습니다.
Understand.
이해하다.
People from which side.
어느 쪽에서 온 사람들.
Military power or Japan?
군사력인가, 일본인가?
At this time it is still unclear.
현재로서는 아직 불분명합니다.
However, you have already entered the range,
그러나 이미 해당 범위에 들어갔습니다.
it's been some time
시간이 좀 지났어
but he never fired.
하지만 그는 결코 해고하지 않았습니다.
He definitely knows
그 사람은 확실히 알고 있어
today you will work together with the boss here,
오늘은 여기 사장님과 함께 일하게 될 거예요.
Want to catch us all at once.
우리 모두를 한 번에 붙잡고 싶습니다.
But they are confused.
그러나 그들은 혼란스러워합니다.
Because there are no superiors and subordinates.
왜냐하면 윗사람과 아랫사람이 없기 때문입니다.
Will meet like us.
우리처럼 만날 거예요.
We look like we're on a date.
우리 데이트하는 것 같아.
Or cheating.
아니면 부정 행위.
Up to them.
그들에게 달려 있습니다.
But they were already suspicious
하지만 그들은 이미 의심을 품고 있었다
to information.
정보에.
But I'm afraid this suspicion is only temporary.
하지만 이런 의심은 일시적일 뿐이라는 게 유감입니다.
Correct.
옳은.
So we must immediately think of a solution.
그러므로 우리는 즉시 해결책을 생각해내야 합니다.
Time and place
시간과 장소
the place is not wrong.
장소는 잘못된 것이 아닙니다.
Team leader Tao,
팀장 타오님,
will shoot or not
쏠까 말까
our goal is to get rid of
우리의 목표는 제거하는 것입니다
and his superiors.
그리고 그의 상사.
If shot now
지금 쏘면
will surprise the real target
진짜 목표를 놀라게 할 것이다
I really didn't think about it
난 정말 그것에 대해 생각하지 않았다
you are a parrot
당신은 앵무새입니다
I didn't think so before either
나도 전에는 그렇게 생각하지 않았어
Plum blossom Four is you.
매화 4위는 바로 당신입니다.
So you already knew my identity from the start?
그럼 당신은 처음부터 내 정체를 이미 알고 있었던 겁니까?
Fourth Comrade Meihua.
네 번째 동지 메이화.
Tell me about the current situation.
현재 상황에 대해 말해주세요.
You've heard about business problems, right?
비즈니스 문제에 대해 들어보셨죠?
I don't have an identity as a cover
커버로서의 아이덴티티가 없어요
Shan Xia also got the medicine formula
Shan Xia도 약을 얻었습니다.
I failed the organization's trust in me.
나는 나에 대한 조직의 신뢰를 잃었습니다.
Initial organizational plan
초기 조직 계획
to tell you to leave Shanghai.
상하이를 떠나라고 합니다.
I once saw Lao Lu writing a work report
나는 라오루가 업무 보고서를 작성하는 것을 본 적이 있다
your work report.
당신의 작업 보고서.
I assumed you wouldn't agree to go.
나는 당신이 가기로 동의하지 않을 것이라고 생각했습니다.
So, I've asked permission from the organization.
그래서 해당 기관에 허가를 요청했습니다.
But now
그러나 지금
now I also have no other way.
이제 나에게도 다른 방법은 없다.
There is one clue
단서가 하나 있다
do you know Xindi?
신디를 아시나요?
Xindi?
신디?
I heard the conversation between the foot of the mountain and Neta.
산기슭과 네타의 대화를 들었습니다.
Yamashita said,
Yamashita said,
we look forward to the opening of the second phase of the Shan Project
Shan 프로젝트의 두 번째 단계가 시작되기를 기대합니다.
is in Xindi.
신디에 있어요.
Unfortunately, after that I was interrupted.
불행히도 그 후 나는 방해를 받았습니다.
I didn't hear the rest of the story.
나머지 이야기는 듣지 못했습니다.
What is that new place
그 새로운 곳은 무엇입니까?
is a place name?
지명이야?
I've checked it.
나는 그것을 확인했다.
Shanghai is no new place.
상하이는 새로운 곳이 아니다.
What's that?
그게 뭐야?
Must be checked clearly.
명확하게 확인해야 합니다.
However, the most important thing now,
그러나 지금 가장 중요한 것은,
must be free from here
여기서부터 자유로워져야 해
what in the box is copper plate?
상자 안에 동판은 뭐예요?
As long as you hand over the box to me,
상자를 나에게 넘겨주기만 하면
then it is clear that I am your superior,
그렇다면 내가 당신의 상사라는 것이 분명합니다.
they will shoot.
그들은 쏠 것입니다.
We can't hand over the copper plates now,
지금은 동판을 넘겨드릴 수 없습니다.
also can't act rashly.
또한 경솔하게 행동할 수도 없다.
Correct.
옳은.
Their main goal is copper.
그들의 주요 목표는 구리입니다.
Then kill us all.
그럼 우리 모두를 죽여라.
Because now I can't confirm my identity
지금은 본인 확인을 할 수 없기 때문에
so they still doubt
그래서 그들은 아직도 의심하고 있어
but if
하지만 만약에
if there's anything we want to leave behind,
우리가 남기고 싶은 것이 있다면,
they won't care too much.
그들은 별로 신경 쓰지 않을 것이다.
Will shoot straight away.
바로 촬영해 드립니다.
You're at three o'clock
넌 3시야
is the Su Zhou river.
소주(蘇州)강이다.
As long as we can jump into the river,
우리가 강에 뛰어들 수 있는 한,
we'll stay out of range of snipers
우리는 저격수의 범위 밖에 있을 거예요
You mean, I took the box and ran to the river embankment?
내가 상자를 들고 강 제방으로 달려갔다는 건가요?
Can't.
캔트.
As soon as you touch the box,
상자를 터치하자마자,
they will shoot you,
그들은 당신을 쏠 것입니다,
I have one way.
나에겐 한 가지 방법이 있다.
What way?
어떤 방법으로?
Did you kiss me?
나한테 키스했어?
Don't dare anymore?
더 이상 감히하지 않습니까?
It seems,
것 같다,
This woman did not come to work together.
이 여자는 함께 일하러 오지 않았습니다.
Target Chen Jia Ping.
타겟 천자핑(Chen Jia Ping).
Why are you angry with me?
왜 나에게 화를 내나요?
They want to run away
그들은 도망가고 싶어해
shot Chen Jia Ping
첸 지아 핑(Chen Jia Ping)을 쐈다
Aim for that woman
그 여자를 노려라
block their escape route.
탈출 경로를 차단하세요.
Don't kill me.
나를 죽이지 마십시오.
My son is only two months old.
제 아들은 이제 태어난 지 두 달밖에 안 됐어요.
Please save us.
우리를 구해주세요.
Running backwards is dangerous.
뒤로 달리는 것은 위험합니다.
How are you?
어떻게 지내세요?
Lu Fang
루팡
protect me!
날 지켜줘!
Jia Ping
지아 핑
It turns out that Chen Jia Ping's boss is you
Chen Jia Ping의 상사가 당신이라는 것이 밝혀졌습니다
It turns out you were the one who betrayed Chen Jia Ping.
Chen Jia Ping을 배신한 사람은 당신이라는 것이 밝혀졌습니다.
Chen Jia Ping dimana?
첸 지아 핑 디마나?
I don't know
모르겠습니다
what happened to him
그에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
don't you know?
모르시나요?
Is he still alive?
그는 아직 살아 있나요?
I don't know.
모르겠습니다.
I only know he's here to help me,
나는 그가 나를 도우려고 여기 있다는 것만 알고 있어요.
actually you really love him
사실 당신은 그 사람을 정말 사랑해요
Is that true?
그게 사실인가요?
I should be the one asking you this.
당신에게 이런 질문을 하는 사람은 바로 나여야 합니다.
Do you really love him
당신은 그를 정말로 사랑합니까?
I love her.
그녀를 사랑합니다.
But I have to kill him
하지만 난 그 사람을 죽여야 해
in here is the copper edition.
여기에는 구리판이 있습니다.
Your evil plan will not work.
당신의 사악한 계획은 성공하지 못할 것입니다.
You won't be able to run away from this either
너도 여기서 도망칠 수는 없을 거야
sooner or later, your crimes
조만간 당신의 범죄
Of course.
물론.
Everyone retreat!
다들 퇴각하세요!
Defeat
패배시키다
defeated!
패배했다!
Possible!
가능한!
Well, look no further.
더 이상 보지 마세요.
Back off, back off.
물러서라, 물러서라.
Go back.
돌아가세요.
Just leave.
그냥 떠나세요.
Left twin.
왼쪽 쌍둥이.
Already home.
이미 집에 있습니다.
I'm not dead.
나는 죽지 않았습니다.
You're very disappointed, right?
많이 실망하셨죠?
You die, I'm more disappointed.
네가 죽어서 내가 더 실망했어.
At least you didn't deny it.
적어도 당신은 그것을 부정하지 않았습니다.
Just like a top secret military agent should do.
일급 비밀 군사 요원이 해야 하는 것과 같습니다.
Tao Dachun definitely wouldn't understand.
타오다춘은 확실히 이해하지 못할 것이다.
He's tried hard
그는 열심히 노력했어요
prepare an ambush
매복을 준비하다
but still can't get rid of you.
하지만 아직도 당신을 제거할 수 없습니다.
Why do that to me?
나한테 왜 그러는 걸까요?
You betrayed me.
넌 나를 배신 했어.
Betraying the trust you built again.
다시 쌓아온 신뢰를 배신합니다.
This has nothing to do with my beliefs.
이것은 내 믿음과 아무 관련이 없습니다.
So what does it have to do with it?
그렇다면 그것이 그것과 무슨 관련이 있습니까?
You killed Captain Liu.
당신은 리우 선장을 죽였습니다.
I must take revenge for him!
나는 그에게 복수해야 한다!
Liu Wuchang is dead.
류우창(劉文昌)이 죽었다.
Why?
왜?
Still don't dare to confess?
아직도 감히 고백하지 못하시나요?
This isn't like you.
이것은 당신과는 다릅니다.
He helped me.
그는 나를 도왔습니다.
Why should I kill him?
내가 왜 그를 죽여야 하나요?
That's why your sins are even more unforgivable.
그렇기 때문에 너희 죄는 더욱 용서받을 수 없다.
I didn't kill him.
나는 그를 죽이지 않았습니다.
I didn't kill Liu Wuchang.
나는 유무창을 죽이지 않았다.
The person who killed him,
그를 죽인 사람,
it must be because he instigated our relationship,
그 사람이 우리 관계를 부추겼기 때문일 거예요.
and incited you to betray and kill me.
나를 배신하고 죽이도록 당신을 선동했습니다.
So it turns out.
그래서 밝혀졌습니다.
You killed Lu Fang
당신이 루팡을 죽였습니다
Lu Fang is dead
루팡은 죽었어
weren't you the one who killed him?
그 사람을 죽인 사람이 당신이 아니었나요?
Team leader Tao.
팀 리더 타오.
I've got the copper plate.
구리판이 있어요.
Good work.
잘 했어.
Dimana Chen Jia Ping?
디마나 첸 지아 핑?
Is dead
죽었어
are you sure?
확실합니까?
If he doesn't die,
그 사람이 죽지 않는다면,
I will find it too
나도 찾아볼게
and killed him with my own hands
그리고 내 손으로 그를 죽였어
Good.
좋은.
What about this woman?
이 여자는 어떻습니까?
Already injured.
이미 부상을 입었습니다.
I will take him away
내가 그를 데려가겠다
Why
왜
I don't want him to die so soon.
나는 그가 그렇게 빨리 죽는 것을 원하지 않습니다.
It turns out you already knew from the start
당신은 이미 처음부터 알고 있었나 보다.
she had an affair with Chen Jia Ping
그녀는 Chen Jia Ping과 바람을 피웠다
Good
좋은
I'll leave him to you.
나는 그를 당신에게 맡길 것입니다.
Resolving old and new grudges together.
오래된 원한과 새로운 원한을 함께 해결합니다.
Copper version?
구리 버전?
Finally back in your hands.
마침내 당신의 손에 돌아왔습니다.
So what was in the box then?
그럼 그 상자 안에는 무엇이 들어 있었나요?
You don't need to care.
걱정할 필요가 없습니다.
I've replaced it with something else
다른걸로 교체했어요
Why?
왜?
Why betray us in the first place
애초에 왜 우리를 배신했는지
now you want to help us?
이제 우리를 도와주시겠어요?
Suddenly I understood one thing
문득 나는 한 가지를 깨달았다
Chen Jia Ping and I have personal grievances
Chen Jia Ping과 저는 개인적인 불만이 있습니다
I cannot be taken advantage of by people with evil intentions
악한 의도를 가진 사람들에게 이용당할 수는 없습니다.
I believe that the Communist Party is justice
나는 공산당이 정의라고 믿는다
believes that the Communist Party can bring hope to China
공산당이 중국에 희망을 가져다줄 수 있다고 믿는다
so I won't let the military get the silver version.
그래서 나는 군대가 실버 버전을 얻지 못하게 할 것입니다.
Will not let their evil plans succeed.
그들의 사악한 계획이 성공하지 못하게 하리라.
You get off here
여기서 내리세요
make sure to take the copper plate back to the border area
동판은 꼭 국경지역으로 가져가세요
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Colleague.
동료.
So what's your next plan?
그럼 다음 계획은 무엇인가요?
Don't know.
모르겠어요.
I have no other way anymore.
더 이상 다른 방법이 없습니다.
Also there is nowhere to go
게다가 갈 곳도 없다.
why do you prefer this dead end
왜 이 막다른 골목을 선호하는가?
rather than believe that Jia Ping had been framed?
Jia Ping이 모함을 받았다고 믿기보다는요?
I rather believe what I see
나는 오히려 내가 보는 것을 믿는다
Jia Ping must still be alive
Jia Ping은 아직 살아 있어야 합니다.
the truth will be revealed someday
진실은 언젠가 밝혀지겠죠
I also hope he lives
그 사람도 살았으면 좋겠어
he should have died in my hands
그 사람은 내 손에 죽었어야 했는데
after that, Lu Fang got out of the car
그 후 Lu Fang은 차에서 내 렸습니다.
what happened again
무슨 일이 또 일어났어?
I wouldn't know.
나는 모른다.
It seems I misunderstood you.
내가 당신을 오해한 것 같습니다.
I also misunderstood you.
나도 당신을 오해했습니다.
It's broken even.
심지어 고장났어요.
My wife,
내 아내,
Remember what I said at the wedding?
내가 결혼식에서 했던 말 기억나?
You're not perfect
당신은 완벽하지 않습니다
I'm not perfect either
나도 완벽하지 않아
however, if we combine,
그러나 결합하면
it's perfect.
그것은 완벽.
But now,
그러나 지금,
not so perfect.
그다지 완벽하지는 않습니다.
Do you still remember?
아직도 기억하시나요?
where we first met?
우리 처음 만난 곳은?
Who's that?
저 사람은 누구야?
Don't.
하지 않다.
Three, two, one.
셋 둘 하나.
Lame!
절뚝거리는!
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Think about why soy milk should be mixed with cakwe.
왜 두유를 cakwe와 섞어야 하는지 생각해 보세요.
You can also add eggs.
계란을 추가할 수도 있습니다.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
It doesn't matter
그것은 중요하지 않습니다
the egg fell.
계란이 떨어졌습니다.
Can add eggs
계란 추가 가능
kill people
사람들을 죽이다
Hurry up
서둘러요
to kill me,
나를 죽이려고,
insert yourself into,
자신을 삽입하고,
tuan Shan Xia.
투안샨샤.
Plum blossom four and red peach blossom five are dead.
매화 네 송이, 홍도 다섯 송이가 죽었습니다.
Are you sure?
확실합니까?
I saw it myself.
나는 그것을 직접 보았다.
As expected.
예상대로.
It turns out they killed each other.
서로를 죽인 것으로 밝혀졌습니다.
Finally die together
결국 같이 죽는다
qian Xiu Cai
치안 슈 카이
You didn't just help me find Lu Fang
당신은 내가 Lu Fang을 찾는 데 도움을 준 것이 아닙니다.
this hidden pkc
이 숨겨진 pkc
have found used copper coins
중고 구리 동전을 발견했습니다
Now
지금
You also helped me defeat plum blossom four and red peach blossom five.
당신은 또한 매화 4화와 붉은 복숭아 5화를 물리치는 데 도움을 주었습니다.
You're very talented.
당신은 매우 재능이 있습니다.
I really admire him
나는 그를 정말로 존경한다
Thank you Mr. Shan Xia.
Shan Xia 씨에게 감사드립니다.
It seems like
그것은 것 같다
Taihe commercial bank manager position
태허상업은행 관리자직
is yours.
당신 것입니다.
It's you
당신이에요
Qian Xiu locked you up here
Qian Xiu가 당신을 여기에 가두었습니다.
it's you
너야
so you too
그러니 너도 마찬가지야
memberitahu Qian Xiu Cai
회원itahu Qian Xiu Cai
My and Shuang Tao's identities
나와 솽타오의 정체
why did you kill Captain Liu?
왜 류 선장을 죽였나요?
I didn't kill.
나는 죽이지 않았습니다.
Isn't it Chen Jia Ping?
천지아핑 아닌가요?
Bukan Chen Jia Ping
부칸 첸 지아 핑
Who
WHO
what do you want to say?
말하고 싶은게 뭡니까?
Director Jiang.
장 감독.
Why did he do that?
왜 그랬나요?
Captain Liu is a traitor.
Liu 선장은 배신자입니다.
Stand up and stand tall.
일어서십시오.
Our beliefs have reached the communist side
우리의 신념은 공산쪽에 이르렀다
bagaimana Jiang Zhaoguo tahu?
바가이마나 Jiang Zhaoguo tahu?
I said it.
내가 말했어.
So, Jiang Zhaoguo was also the one who told you to lie
그럼 당신에게 거짓말을 하라고 한 사람도 장자오궈였군요
harm Chen Jia Ping.
Chen Jia Ping에게 해를 끼칩니다.
Is it true
사실인가요?
if I don't do it,
내가 하지 않으면,
ketua Jiang akan membunuh Zhou Qingfang
Ketua Jiang Akan membunuh Zhou Qingfang
so Qian Xiu killed Lu Fang
그래서 Qian Xiu는 Lu Fang을 죽였습니다.
and blamed Zuo Shuang Tao.
Zuo Shuang Tao를 비난했습니다.
Right?
오른쪽?
Qian Xiu Cai
치안 슈 카이
is a demon
악마다
also a talented person
역시 능력있는 사람
he did many things to be proud of
그는 자랑스러워할 만한 일을 많이 했다
but no one told him.
하지만 아무도 그에게 말하지 않았습니다.
He kept looking for me to talk
그 사람은 계속 나랑 얘기하려고 찾았어
I know everything.
나는 모든 것을 알고 있습니다.
And agree to one of my requests.
그리고 내 요청 중 하나에 동의하세요.
I will tell you.
난 당신을 말할 것이다.
What conditions?
어떤 조건이 있나요?
Let go.
가자.
What about Captain Liu's letter?
Liu 선장의 편지는 어떻습니까?
Captain Liu Quotes
Liu 선장이 인용합니다.
is me.
나야.
Forged.
서서히 나아가는.
I've studied handwriting
나는 손글씨를 공부했어요
and very expert in
그리고 매우 전문적인
where was that letter before?
그 편지는 전에 어디에 있었나요?
Director Jiang burned the letter.
장 국장은 편지를 불태웠다.
What's in the letter?
편지에는 무엇이 들어있나요?
Tell me.
말해 주세요.
Captain Liu said,
류 선장이 말했다.
I hope you can follow the faith
믿음을 따를 수 있기를 바랍니다
and your dreams.
그리고 당신의 꿈.
At the end of the letter,
편지의 마지막에는,
he gave you a poem.
그는 당신에게 시를 주었습니다.
Don't hear the sound of leaves breaking through the forest
숲을 뚫고 나뭇잎이 부서지는 소리가 들리지 않는다
Why not shout and keep moving
소리를 지르고 계속 움직여 보세요
Your wounds are very serious.
당신의 상처는 매우 심각합니다.
Can't live much longer.
더 이상 살 수 없습니다.
I know
알아요
Your stab today almost killed me.
오늘 네 찔림으로 인해 거의 죽을 뻔 했어.
Which puncture?
어떤 구멍이 났나요?
That stab
그 찌르기
aren't you avoiding it?
피하고 있는 거 아냐?
If I don't run away,
내가 도망치지 않는다면,
won't you be a widow?
너 과부가 되지 않을래?
I'm sure you'll avoid it.
나는 당신이 그것을 피할 것이라고 확신합니다.
Oh God.
오 맙소사.
Too scary.
너무 무섭다.
How did you know?
어떻게 알았나요?
While I'm waiting for you at home,
집에서 당신을 기다리는 동안,
keep thinking
계속 생각해
things that have happened,
일어난 일들,
I'm just thinking
난 그냥 생각 중이야
Open the window to breathe fresh air.
창문을 열어 신선한 공기를 마시세요.
Then I saw
그러다가 봤어
opposite is the reflection from the telescope.
그 반대는 망원경의 반사이다.
Suddenly I understood
문득 이해가 되었어요
this is not as simple as I thought
이건 생각보다 간단하지 않아
I was too stupid before.
예전에는 내가 너무 멍청했어요.
Of course.
물론.
I went to find Hu Jun.
후준을 찾으러 갔어요.
He has also confessed.
그는 또한 고백했습니다.
Still can.
아직도 할 수 있습니다.
Not that stupid.
그렇게 바보는 아닙니다.
How about you?
당신은 어떤가요?
I am...
그래요...
I see
알겠어요
I saw the knife stuck in Lu Fang's body
루팡의 몸에 칼이 박혀있는 걸 봤어
honestly a second
솔직히 잠깐
I did suspect you.
나는 당신을 의심했습니다.
But after I thought carefully
그런데 곰곰히 생각해보니
even if you really kill Lu Fang
정말로 Lu Fang을 죽인다고 해도
You wouldn't be so stupid as to leave the knife at the scene, right?
현장에 칼을 두고 갈 정도로 멍청하진 않겠죠?
When I came home, I saw you carrying a knife
집에 오니 칼을 들고 있는 걸 봤어
peeling apples.
사과 껍질 벗기기.
I'm certain
나는 확신 해
The person who killed Lu Fang wasn't you.
Lu Fang을 죽인 사람은 당신이 아니었어요.
You didn't realize it anyway?
그런데도 그걸 깨닫지 못하셨나요?
It's too quiet around our house
우리 집 주변은 너무 조용해요
silence that never existed.
존재하지 않았던 침묵.
This means that from the start there were people organizing the defense.
이는 처음부터 방어를 조직하는 사람들이 있었다는 것을 의미합니다.
do you know
당신은 알고 있나요
actually,
실제로,
when you say we're not perfect at this point,
당신이 지금 우리가 완벽하지 않다고 말할 때,
I already understand what you mean.
나는 당신이 무슨 뜻인지 이미 이해합니다.
However there are a few things
그러나 몇 가지 사항이 있습니다.
which cannot be said directly.
직접적으로 말할 수는 없는 일이다.
What if there are eavesdroppers?
도청자가 있다면 어떨까요?
Compact?
콤팩트?
Satu Qian Xiu Cai
사투 첸 시우 카이
one country of Zhao
조나라(趙國)
create your own tactics
자신만의 전술을 만들어 보세요
to incite us both
우리 둘 다 자극하려고
to kill each other.
서로를 죽이려고.
Fortunately,
다행스럽게도,
we choose to trust each other
우리는 서로를 믿기로 결정했습니다
but now it's still not perfect
하지만 지금은 아직 완벽하지 않아
under the mountain.
산 아래.
Sell, sell.
팔아라, 팔아라.
Movie star Han Lu marries a rich Japanese merchant,
영화배우 한루는 일본의 부유한 상인과 결혼하고,
The wedding party will be held soon.
곧 결혼식이 열릴 예정이다.
I suddenly want to drink coffee.
갑자기 커피가 마시고 싶어지네요.
You just wait for me in the car.
당신은 차에서 나를 기다리기만 하면 됩니다.
Good.
좋은.
If you really marry Takeshi Yamashita,...
정말로 야마시타 타케시와 결혼한다면...
You will become a notorious traitor.
당신은 악명 높은 배신자가 될 것입니다.
You will forever be nailed to the pillar of shame.
너는 영원히 수치의 기둥에 못 박힐 것이다.
Do you know?
당신은 알고 있나요?
I always disappoint you,
나는 항상 당신을 실망시킵니다.
makes you hurt,
당신을 아프게 하고,
It's because I endured too much
너무 많이 참았기 때문이야
I carry too much burden.
나는 짐을 너무 많이 지고 있다.
Now it's different.
이제는 달라졌습니다.
Now the mission is a complete failure.
이제 임무는 완전히 실패했습니다.
I also have no face to return to Chongqing.
나 역시 충칭으로 돌아갈 얼굴이 없다.
In my life,
내 인생에서,
now you are the only one.
이제 당신은 유일한 사람입니다.
Which makes us forget everything.
그것은 우리로 하여금 모든 것을 잊게 만듭니다.
Looking for a place where no one knows us,
우리를 아는 사람이 아무도 없는 곳을 찾고,
and start a new life.
그리고 새로운 삶을 시작하세요.
Good?
좋은?
This is a plane ticket to Hong Kong.
홍콩행 비행기표입니다.
I will be waiting for you.
나는 당신을 기다리고 있을 것입니다.
Always waiting for you.
항상 당신을 기다리고 있습니다.
Friends
친구
it's time for battle.
이제 전투를 할 시간이다.
Welcome to join our fight.
우리의 싸움에 동참한 것을 환영합니다.
This is Gao Fang.
가오팡입니다.
He intercepted important information with the radio.
그는 라디오로 중요한 정보를 가로채었습니다.
Dear friends,
친애하는 친구,
we have been misled before.
우리는 전에도 오해를 받았습니다.
A new place is not a place
새로운 장소는 장소가 아니다
but rather a film that preaches military doctrine.
오히려 군사 교리를 설교하는 영화입니다.
The name of this film is Xindi
이 영화의 이름은 신디(Xindi)입니다.
Apart from that, this film
그 외에도 이 영화는
will be released soon at Luhua cinemas.
곧 Luhua 영화관에서 개봉될 예정입니다.
I've also targeted
나도 타겟으로 삼았어
the counterfeit money factory is in the underground of the Lu Hua cinema.
위조지폐 공장은 루화(Lu Hua) 영화관 지하에 있어요.
Tomorrow at two o'clock in the afternoon,
내일 오후 2시,
karasuno dan Hanlu
karasuno dan Hanlu
residence at the foot of Shanghai mountain.
상하이 산 기슭에 거주.
Will hold a traditional Japanese wedding ceremony.
일본 전통 결혼식을 거행합니다.
After that, they would go to Lu Hua cinema
그 후 그들은 Lu Hua 영화관에 갔습니다.
to hold an open wedding party.
공개 결혼식을 열다.
After dinner,
저녁 식사 후,
team commander Hata Junliu from Shanghai
팀 사령관 하타 준류(상하이 출신)
will arrive at the location.
해당 장소에 도착하게 됩니다.
Signed a film investment agreement with Yamashita.
야마시타와 영화 투자 계약을 체결했다.
Film investment is a cover.
영화 투자는 표지입니다.
The essence of this agreement...
이번 합의의 핵심은…
Regarding the launch of the second phase of the Shan Project.
Shan 프로젝트의 두 번째 단계 시작에 관해.
So our target this time,
그래서 이번에 우리의 목표는
save workers and members
노동자와 회원을 저장
and experts.
그리고 전문가들.
Then, it will output
그러면 출력됩니다.
minted coins,
주조된 동전,
and printing equipment.
및 인쇄 장비.
Destroy
파괴하다
however, there are actually still two major difficulties
그러나 실제로는 여전히 두 가지 큰 어려움이 있습니다.
which cannot be solved.
해결할 수 없는 것.
The underground counterfeit money factory is divided into two areas,
지하위조화공장은 두 구역으로 나누어져 있는데,
factory,
공장,
member workspace.
회원 작업공간.
There is a wall-shaped safe
벽모양의 금고가 있어요
we go through the explosion
우리는 폭발을 겪는다
we can enter the worker's printing place,
작업자의 인쇄소에 들어갈 수 있습니다.
while expert studios...
전문 스튜디오에서는...
There is an iron door five centimeters thick
두께 5cm의 철문이 있어요
can it explode?
폭발할 수 있나요?
Want to blow up this iron gate,
이 철문을 폭파하고 싶다.
it would take at least ten kilograms
적어도 10킬로그램은 필요할 거예요
up to ten kilograms
최대 10킬로그램
even if we blow up the iron gate
철문을 폭파해도
under the influence of strong air flow
강한 공기 흐름의 영향으로
the people inside had no chance of surviving
안에 있는 사람들은 살아남을 가능성이 전혀 없었어요
the only way
유일한 방법
is to take the lock of the iron door.
철문의 자물쇠를 가져가는 것입니다.
But the key is in the hands of the foot of the mountain.
그러나 열쇠는 산기슭의 손에 있습니다.
Good.
좋은.
Tuan Shan Xia.
투안샨샤.
Because the country of Zhao no longer had any value
조나라에는 더 이상 가치가 없었기 때문이다.
I don't understand.
모르겠어요.
Why do you want to marry Han Lu?
왜 한루와 결혼하고 싶나요?
Now I need it
이제 필요해
Chinese film star.
중국 영화배우.
Specialized in making films with the spirit of the Japanese empire
일제의 정신을 담은 영화제작 전문
useful for paralyzing the Chinese mind
중국인의 마음을 마비시키는데 유용하다
I understand.
이해합니다.
There's one thing
한 가지가 있어요
I'm just telling you.
나는 단지 당신에게 말하고 있습니다.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
I like.
좋아요.
Leaving
퇴거
on Han Lu's body.
한루의 몸에.
It turns out
그것은 밝혀
scars can make a woman
상처가 여자를 만들 수도 있다
a woman.
여자.
Kimono has no pockets
기모노에는 주머니가 없습니다
always carry important items,
항상 중요한 물건을 가지고 다니고,
usually put in Xin Xuan's pocket.
보통 Xin Xuan의 주머니에 넣습니다.
Small seeds.
작은 씨앗.
Later at 4 o'clock
나중에 4시쯤
We must complete tasks on time
우리는 제 시간에 작업을 완료해야 합니다
after completing today's tasks,
오늘의 일을 마치고,
we will leave Shanghai.
우리는 상하이를 떠날 것이다.
I will take you back to my hometown.
나는 당신을 고향으로 데려다 줄 것입니다.
Where is my hometown?
내 고향은 어디인가요?
In the beautiful Sungai Panas.
아름다운 Sungai Panas에서.
My hometown is very beautiful.
내 고향은 매우 아름답습니다.
Meadow
목초지
there is a lake
호수가 있어요
the grass there is most fertile.
그곳의 풀은 가장 비옥합니다.
The water there is the sweetest.
거기 물이 제일 맛있어요.
You can eat until you are full every day.
매일 배가 부를 때까지 먹을 수 있습니다.
And drink until it's full.
그리고 가득 찰 때까지 마신다.
Then keep running, keep running.
그럼 계속 달리세요, 계속 달리세요.
Keep running until the moon rises
달이 뜰 때까지 계속 달려라
the meadow will be very peaceful.
초원은 매우 평화로울 것이다.
I can take you to eat roast mutton
양고기 구이를 먹으러 데려갈 수 있어요
Correct.
옳은.
You don't eat meat
당신은 고기를 먹지 않습니다
you just like eating grass.
넌 그냥 풀 먹는 걸 좋아하는구나.
I've been careless these past few years,
지난 몇 년간 부주의하게 지냈어요.
maybe work for Japanese people.
어쩌면 일본인을 위해 일할 수도 있습니다.
Almost made a big mistake
거의 큰 실수를 할 뻔했어요
so I want to sit in the village meadow
그래서 난 마을 초원에 앉아 있고 싶어
see the moon in the sky
하늘에 있는 달을 보아라
Introspect yourself well.
자신을 잘 성찰해보세요.
Why
왜
are you looking down on me?
너 나를 내려다보고 있는 거야?
You're almost a Japanese horse too.
당신도 거의 일본 말입니다.
So you also have to introspect yourself
그러니 당신도 자신을 성찰해야 한다.
even though Chen Jia Ping is very fierce towards me
Chen Jia Ping이 나에게 매우 맹렬하지만
but he is a good person
하지만 그 사람은 좋은 사람이야
I really envy him.
나는 그를 정말로 부러워한다.
Amazed about what?
무엇에 놀랐나요?
Become a hero.
영웅이 되세요.
It definitely feels good.
확실히 기분이 좋아요.
Especially after becoming a hero and returning home,
특히 영웅이 되어 집으로 돌아온 후,
there is still a beautiful wife who warms his blanket.
아직도 담요를 따뜻하게 해주는 아름다운 아내가 있습니다.
Correct.
옳은.
Don't I still have you?
아직 당신이 없나요?
Xiao Douzi.
샤오두지.
The days ahead,
앞으로 며칠,
we will both get through it.
우리 둘 다 이겨낼 거예요.
Wretched.
비참한.
The key was not in Xin Xuan's bag.
열쇠는 Xin Xuan의 가방에 없었습니다.
Xiao Douzi.
샤오두지.
We're about to leave.
우리는 곧 떠날 예정이다.
Leave
떠나다
How about this?
이건 어때?
Where can I get the key?
열쇠는 어디서 구할 수 있나요?
Xiao Douzi, kembali
샤오두지, 켐발리
return
반품
don't shoot.
쏘지 마세요.
Don't shoot
쏘지 마세요
heart
마음
what happened?
무슨 일이에요?
Xiao Douzi.
샤오두지.
Accordingly.
따라서.
Lord under the mountain.
산 아래 주님.
Lord under the mountain?
산 아래 주님?
Owned by Han Lu.
한루 소유.
Here.
여기.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Two punctures.
구멍이 두 개 있습니다.
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
Sorry, everyone.
죄송해요 여러분.
The horse was a little scared.
말은 조금 겁을 먹었습니다.
It doesn't hurt anything, right?
아무 것도 아프지 않죠?
I ask you,
나는 당신에게 묻습니다.
why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
I work here.
나 여기서 일한다.
This...
이것...
Famous artist's wooden leg
유명한 예술가의 나무 다리
tuan Shan Xia
투안 샨 시아
these two knives
이 두 개의 칼
has a bad habit of stealing women's things.
여자 물건을 훔치는 나쁜 버릇이 있어요.
Very fragrant.
매우 향기로운.
Tuan Shan Xia.
투안샨샤.
Today is our big day.
오늘은 우리의 중요한 날입니다.
Don't shoot me, okay?
날 쏘지 마세요, 알았죠?